nashvillewraps.com 2019-04-03

# Nashville Wraps Privacy Policy | Nashville Wraps

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice and privacy policy (this “Policy”) explaining our online information practices through the website or service linking to this Policy (the “Site”) and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.   The Site is operated by or on behalf of Nashville Wraps (“Nashville Wraps,” “we,” “us,” “our”). 

WE MAY MODIFY THIS POLICY AT ANY TIME AT OUR DISCRETION, AND SUCH MODIFICATIONS ARE EFFECTIVE UPON BEING POSTED ON THE SITE.  YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR REVIEWING THIS POLICY PERIODICALLY TO ENSURE THAT YOU ARE AWARE OF ANY CHANGES TO IT BECAUSE YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THE SITE WILL MEAN THAT YOU ACCEPT SUCH CHANGES.  **IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS POLICY OR ANY SUBSEQUENT CHANGES TO THIS POLICY, YOU MUST NOT ACCESS OR USE THE SITE OR DISCLOSE ANY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION THROUGH THE SITE.**

**_Policy last updated and effective as of February 1, 2018._**

## The Information We Collect

This Policy applies to all information collected or submitted on the Site, or any website or subdomain related to any of our products, but does not apply to information collected via other methods or offline. On some pages of the Site, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected through these pages include (but are not limited to):

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Username and Password
  * Credit/Debit Card Information

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a product on behalf of another business or other recipient and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected include (but are not limited to):

  * Recipient’s Name
  * Recipient’s Address  

  * Recipient’s Phone Number

We may also use anonymous information collected in connection with your visits to the Site.  Anonymous information is data that does not contain information that identifies an individual.  Anonymous information can include certain personal information that has been de-identified; that is, information that has been rendered anonymous. It may include such information as your browser type, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your geolocation, browser type, device type, or information related to your use of the Site, such as the page served, time of request, preceding page viewed, referring web site address, and other similar information, and may include the use of Cookies, as described below.  Anonymous information is used internally for administration of Site, troubleshooting, and to help improve the quality of Site and their design. We also use non-personally identifiable information to help analyze trends and statistics, protect the security and integrity of Sites, evaluate our online marketing campaigns, and tailor our promotions or other offers to you.

A "Cookie" is a small text file which a web site employs to use applications that require multi-page submissions and queries. Cookies will not damage or erase files on your computer. Nashville Wraps uses Cookies to make our tools and services easier to use. Cookies are the best way to offer you a hassle-free experience by retaining information about your purchase selections. This information may be combined with your personal information (such as demographic and past purchase information) from our records and other sources. Such information about your use of the Site will become part of your profile as maintained by Nashville Wraps.

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself or others for purposes including processing and fulfilling orders, communicating with you, responding to inquiries regarding your order, providing updates on our new products and services, account registration and maintenance, and administration of the Site.  For example, we use information you provide when placing an order to complete that order and confirm delivery. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. In addition, we may allow you to register with our Site if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services and we will then send you period communications via email or other delivery methods regarding our new products and services. 

In addition, we may from time to time contract with third parties to assist us in collecting, maintaining and managing our customer information, taking and fulfilling orders, processing credit card information, and providing analytics regarding your interactions with our Site and other third-party websites so that we may improve the products and services we offer you. We also may use Google Analytics, a service provided by Google, Inc., to gather information about how you and other users engage with the App and Platform. For more information about Google Analytics, please visit [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites). 

**We do not sell or rent customer information to third parties for marketing purposes.**

We may also disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (a) comply with the law or with legal process; (b) protect and defend our rights and property; (c) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of Site; or (d) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through the Site.

## Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## You Are In Control

From time to time, Nashville Wraps conducts market research or sends email to introduce new products and/or services that may be of interest to you. You can choose not to receive this correspondence. Simply go to the My Account page and opt out of "Receive Promotional Email" or you may use the convenient opt-out link at the bottom of our promotional emails. Once you opt-out, you will not receive any promotional emails from Nashville Wraps unless you opt back in at a later time. You will still be a registered member of Nashville Wraps and eligible to use any of our products and services.  
You should take precautions to protect the security of your username and password.  To help secure your access, we recommend that you do not share your username or password.

## Special Notice to Non-U.S. Visitors and Customers

If you are located outside the United States of America and are visiting the Site, you should be aware that your personal information will be transferred to the United States of America, the laws of which may be deemed by the your country to have inadequate data protection. If you are located in a country outside the United States of America and voluntarily submit personal information to us, you thereby consent to the general use of such information as provided in this Policy and to the transfer of that information to, and/or storage of that information in, the United States of America.

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at - [webpolicy@nashvillewraps.com](mailto:webpolicy@nashvillewraps.com)
